[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "console.log(typeof NaN)",
    "answers": ["undefined", "NaN", "string", "number"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "3 + 2 + '7'",
    "answers": ["12", "327", "57", "NaN"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "let a = 10;\nlet b = () => {\n  console.log(this.a);\n}\nb();",
    "answers": ["undefined", "null", "10", "ReferenceError"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "1 + 2 + '3' + 4 + 5",
    "answers": ["'3345'", "15", "NaN", "Error"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "2 > '3'",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "undefined", "NaN"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "const arr = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\nconst [x, y, ...rest] = arr;\nconsole.log(rest.length);",
    "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "'2' + 3 * 4",
    "answers": ["14", "20", "26", "Error"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr[10] = 10;\nconsole.log(arr.length);",
    "answers": ["3", "10", "11", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "console.log(0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3)",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "undefined", "NaN"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "[] + []",
    "answers": ["[]", "''", "undefined", "NaN"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
    "code": "'foo' instanceof String",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "null", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
    "code": "const arr1 = [1, 2, 3];\nconst arr2 = [4, 5, 6];\nconst arr3 = [...arr1, ...arr2];\nconsole.log(arr3);",
    "answers": [
      "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]",
      "[[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6]]",
      "[[1, 2, 3], 4, 5, 6]",
      "[1, 2, 3, [4, 5, 6]]"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]
